(Penny:)I love San Francisco.
I wish I was going with you.
(Sheldon:)I understand your envy.
(Sheldon:)This is a can't-miss symposium.
(Sheldon:)There are going to be discussions
on bioorganic cellular computer devices...
(Sheldon:)...advancements
in multi-threaded task completion...
...plus a round table on the non-equilibrium
Green's Function approach...
(Sheldon:)...to the photoionization process
in atoms.
(Penny:)When I go, I usually just get hammered
and ride the cable cars.
This conference is a big thing.
(Leonard:)The keynote address
is delivered by George Smoot.
(Penny:)Oh, my God. The George Smoot?
- You've heard of him?
- Of course I haven't.
(Leonard:)George Smoot
is a Nobel Prize-winning physicist...
(Sheldon:)...one of the great minds of our time.
(Sheldon:)His work in black body form...
(Sheldon:)...and anisotropy of the cosmic
microwave background radiation...
(Sheldon:)...cemented our understanding
of the origin of the universe.
(Penny:)It's kind of a funny name though.
(Leonard:)Smoot.
(Sheldon:)It's like talking to a chimp.
(Penny:)Okay, now that I've been completely
insulted, have a good flight.
- Yeah, I wish.
- We're not flying. We're taking the train.
(Penny:)Oh, cool.
(Howard:)Yeah, cool. Seven times as long as flying
and costs almost twice as much.
- Well then why are you doing it?
- Well, we had a vote.
Three voted for airplane,
Sheldon voted for train.
(Leonard:)So we're taking the train.
Don't say it like that, Leonard.
Say it like, "We're taking the train!"